

ABOUT ME

I am determined to take a bold step towards software testing and quality assurance. Thanks to my curiosity and very good work organization, I know that I will be able to handle reporting and documenting test results. My experience as an Office Manager, enriched with an intensive "Manual Tester" course, inspires me to take on new challenges as a QA. I am also actively preparing for the ISTQB exam, expanding my competences.

SKILLS

- JIRA & GIT
- manual testing skills
- Postman
- basic knowledge of SQL
- · testing in the BDD methodology
- **ECDL** certificate
- knowledge of rental law
- MS Office and Google Workspace
- Saldeo smart
- focus on quality
- accuracy and attention to detail
- knowledge expansion and selfdevelopment
- GOE Poland title "The most Can Do Person of 2023"

Languages

- Polish native
- English B2
- Russian A1

Dorota Załucka



+48 883 448 106



zalucka.d.97@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/dorota-zalucka

SELECTED WORK EXPERIENCE

Office Manager

07/2023 - ongoing GOE Poland sp. z o.o.

- Office and correspondence management.
- Issuing invoices, maintaining a register and entering invoices into the system.
- Office management.
- Maintaining office and personnel documentation.
- Cooperation with HR, accounting and legal departments.
- Writing official letters.
- · Conducting recruitment.
- Close cooperation with the management, creating summaries and reports.
- Organizing and coordinating business trips.
- Calendar management.

Property Management Expert 10/2019 - 07/2023 Homfi sp. z o.o.

- Management of rental properties.
- Telephone and e-mail customer service.
- Verification of lease documentation.
- · Conducting training on lease agreement verification and supporting new employees in the buddy system.
- Coordinating the work of the agreement verification team.
- Close cooperation with agents, sales support and service department and legal department.
- · Creating procedures, reports and audits.
- Settlement of utilities and payment of utility bills.
- Organization of repairs.
- Support for other teams.

EDUCATION

Software tester 11/2023 - 03/2024

Software Development Academy

- Test design techniques
- · Testing tools
- · Introduction to programming
- Selenium WebDriver basics
- Testing in BDD tetodes
- Basics of databases

Finance and Accounting 2018 - 2021 **Cracow University of**

• Bachelor's degree: Accounting and financial auditing

Economics